<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<catalog xmlns="http://task1.kirova.htp.by">
    <category Name="Movie">
        <subCategory Name="Action">
            <news Name="Avengers Producer Says Infinity War Is One Big CGI Scene" Provider="Joseph Holland" DateOfIssue="2018-01-01">
                <NewsBody>
                    Newly released commentary on Avengers: Infinity War reveals just how much of the film is CGI...
                    and the answer may be even more than audieces might expect. Along with Avengers: Infinity War's home
                    release, Marvel has created a ton of new material, including deleted scenes, audio commentary, and
                    the
                    "Beyond the Battle" featurettes, which explore the creation of key scenes in the film.
                    This supplementary material contains wealth of new information about the third Avengers film.
                </NewsBody>
            </news>
            <news Name="Boogeyman Pop Trailer Is Drenched in Skull-Crushing Depravity" Provider="Karl Bing" DateOfIssue="2018-01-01">
                <NewsBody>
                    The Boogeyman Pop teaser trailer is here. The upcoming horror anthology was produced independently
                    and was made on a shoestring budget. When the movie was roughly 75 percent through filming, they
                    had spent just $75 thousand, which, as director Brad Michael Elmore puts it, is the catering budget
                    on many movies. Now, the general public is getting a look at what Elmore cooked up with this first
                    full teaser, which looks like it's going to be bizarre, bloody and quite possibly a lot of fun.
                </NewsBody>
            </news>
        </subCategory>
        <subCategory Name="Thriller">
            <news Name="Fan Gives Venom Eyeballs And The Photos Are Hilarious" Provider="Karl Bing" DateOfIssue="2018-01-01">
                <NewsBody>
                    While the latest trailer for the film displays Venom's chaotic and violent nature, the
                    now-popular Twitter post by Matthew Gaydos reveals a sillier take on the character. With the
                    caption, "But what if Venom had eyes?", this photo joins the conversation surrounding the
                    character's appearance in the film, but adds a humorous sidebar to give fans a laugh after
                    viewing the intense new footage.
                </NewsBody>
            </news>
        </subCategory>
    </category>
    <category Name="Disc">
        <subCategory Name="Rock">
            <news Name="Muse 'Simulation Theory' Confirmed November 2018" Provider="Leslie Arkett" DateOfIssue="2018-01-01">
                <NewsBody>
                    Muse's eighth studio album, nicknamed by Dom the 'I Don't Wanna Ruin It For Everyone' album, is
                    the proper follow up to Drones, will be released in 2018. The album deals with the themes of virtual
                    reality, simulated reality and about 'the idea of fantasy becoming real', as mentioned by Matt in an
                    interview, he also mentioned that another reason of writing this album was because 'simulations are
                    becoming something that’s part of our everyday life.
                </NewsBody>
            </news>
            <news Name="The Prodigy announce new album, No Tourists" Provider="Iris West-Allen" DateOfIssue="2018-01-01">
                <NewsBody>
                    The Prodigy are about to release their seventh album, No Tourists.
                    No Tourists is due out on November 2nd on their own label Take Me To The Hospital, and it follows
                    their last album, 2016's The Day Is My Enemy. According to the press release, this record focuses
                    mostly on the band's core trio—Liam Howlett, Maxim and Keith Flint—without much in the way of outside
                    collaborators.
                </NewsBody>
            </news>
        </subCategory>
    </category>
    <category Name="Book">
        <subCategory Name="Fantasy">
            <news Name="Harry Potter latest: New chapter created using only predictive text is now circulating the internet" Provider="Camilla Rutherford" DateOfIssue="2018-01-01">
                <NewsBody>
                    A new chapter in the Harry Potter series has been created using a predictive keyboard -
                    and it's perfect. Botnik Studios, a creative collective which describes itself as "a community of
                    writers, artists and developers collaborating with machines to create strange new things", developed
                    a predictive keyboard to craft sentences using an algorithm. According to Botnik co-founder Jamie Brew,
                    The Predictive Writer scans text for patterns and then generates more text based on the previous words.
                </NewsBody>
            </news>
        </subCategory>
        <subCategory Name="Comics">
            <news Name="First Look: Julie and Shawna Benson Take on Green Arrow" Provider="Lola Tesla" DateOfIssue="2018-01-01">
                <NewsBody>
                    GREEN ARROW #43 marks the debut of writers Julie and Shawna Benson and artist Javier Fernandez
                    on the series, and it finds Ollie going strong in his mission to protect and fight for the people of
                    his city. But he’s not the only one. A new vigilante called the Citizen has also taken up the charge,
                    and it becomes clear pretty quickly that he’s no friend to Oliver Queen. Combine with Ollie and Dinah
                    starting to get serious about their relationship and it’s clear that Green Arrow’s already complicated
                    life is about to get…well, you can figure it out.
                    But what we couldn’t figure out is what changes we could expect when the BATGIRL AND THE BIRDS OF PREY
                    writers make the jump to GREEN ARROW. So, we sat down with them at San Diego Comic-Con to discuss all
                    things Ollie, including what getting serious with Ollie means for Dinah, whether their debut story was
                    inspired by real-world events and exactly what it would be like to work for Oliver Queen.
                </NewsBody>
            </news>
            <news Name="The One TRUE Flash is Coming To DC Comics" Provider="Iris West-Allen" DateOfIssue="2018-01-01">
                <NewsBody>
                    The one true Flash, whoever that may be, is coming to the world DC Comics. Currently, DC Comics'
                    solo The Flash series is in the middle of a storyline called "Flash War," which pits several Scarlet
                    Speedsters against each other. The by.htp.kirova.task1.main conflict has been between Wally West, the original version,
                    and his uncle, Barry Allen.
                </NewsBody>
            </news>
        </subCategory>
    </category>
</catalog>
